Please select a card.
The 33rd single hit song
This time, Nagi Inoue, who is the first
center, is out in the countryside.
A new song campaign to thank 33 people
who helped me and my friends.
I met many friends and benefactors so
far.
The journey of following the roots of
Inoue is finally over tonight.
Can the 33 people who have been aiming
achieve it?
There are 9 people left.
If you ask the person who helped you
here,
Mom
Mom is really anything for me.
I have this every morning.
It's funny to see who's doing this.
I really thought so.
It's like a diary.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
Is this your family?
Yes.
I'm a dog.
Thank you.
I understand.
The family that Inoue is most grateful
for is a family of all.
First, Inoue introduces her family.
He is my younger brother.
When I go home, he is the one who is
most happy and the second one.
He usually comes to my house when I say
welcome home.
He came with me.
He said, what did you buy?
He is very generous.
I don't know him.
He is a very nice person.
We went to see a movie together.
We went to see the final day of the
anime movie in Shibuya.
We ate a lot of popcorn.
He is always like that.
I'm really embarrassed.
What did you do?
I was just playing around.
You are so quiet.
I'm embarrassed to call him my father.
It's hard to explain my father and my
big brother.
Surprisingly, he is very happy with my
activities.
I noticed that he was using his
smartphone screen.
His smartphone case is similar to mine.
I thought it was mine, so I looked at
it.
He is always like that.
He doesn't talk much, but he is
surprisingly happy.
When I show my mom that I took a video,
she looks at me from behind.
I'm happy about that.
I want to show my mom that.
I haven't been able to get out of my
dad's rebellious period.
I was still a child.
I bumped into him a lot.
I still have a lot of things I don't
want to change.
I'm still active in a good way.
He has been very nice to me.
He told me that I was wrong when I was
wrong.
He talked to me until I understood.
He was very supportive.
I want him to be nice to me every time I
bump into him.
But in the end, I'm glad that he was
nice to me.
I'm glad that he is a good person.
I'm glad that he is a big person.
I didn't like him when I was a child.
But now I'm glad that he says that only
parents can do that.
I'm glad that he is a good person.
I was opposed to it.
I remember being opposed to it.
I still wanted to be a child.
I also had other things I wanted to do.
I thought it was a scary world because I
didn't know.
But no matter how much I talked, my will
didn't change.
I thought I had to support her.
But I didn't think I would pass.
I really didn't think I would pass.
I thought I wouldn't be able to enter
the audition.
I told her every time that I don't think
I can pass because I don't look like
Nogitaka.
I told her that I didn't think I could
pass.
I went to the post office every day.
The first time I passed was not by mail,
but by letter.
It was so late that I couldn't get it.
I was so excited every day.
I opened the post office when I left
home.
I opened the post office when I came
back and went to the school.
I kept doing that.
I was so excited that I thought I would
pass.
I don't think I can pass to my father.
You passed to Nancy, so you should pass
to your father.
It was quite difficult.
I told her that I wanted to hide it.
I probably hid it from me at first.
But I couldn't do it well at first.
I asked my mom for help on my phone.
I was like, what?
She was very opposed to it.
I got a letter from Sony Music without
my father knowing.
I told my father that I didn't know what
it was.
I pretended not to know.
But he found out.
I went online because of the corona.
He said, don't come in.
It was hard to explain.
I had to take the exam at home.
I didn't want my siblings to know.
So, I didn't know.
He said, I didn't know.
He wanted me to say that.
I didn't know until he said I passed.
I was shocked that he didn't tell me.
I'm sorry.
You are young.
My father was like, it's okay.
It looks fun.
But my mom was worried.
I was worried, too.
I think my mom was worried.
But she helped me a lot.
If my mom didn't oppose it,
I would have thought more about it.
I think it was a big decision.
My mom made the decision.
But I think my father made the decision.
I think I have both.
I'm sorry.
You know...
I think I like Nagi the most.
We haven't even started yet.
As far as I can see, I don't know if
he's doing anything in the Nogizaka.
I was like, really?
Is it okay? Can he do it?
But I went to see his first performance
in Okinawa.
The other day?
Yes.
I was more impressed that he was
standing in the middle of the stage than
I imagined.
He is usually a child, so I can't see
his hard work.
Even his parents can't see it.
So I tend to hide it.
I'm glad that I'm doing my best.
I'm glad that I'm growing up more and
more.
I'm glad to see the center of the team.
I'm glad.
And a new song campaign to thank the
most important family.
PR for a new song to this store that has
always wanted to be a family.
The bullet local trip ends here.
But what if you sing that you still have
two people?
Yes, but today's location is also the
same.
I'm in trouble with the staff during
construction.
Thank you always.
A new song campaign that has been
decided to be a family.
I go to see the post many times.
That episode is a little bit.
It's more cool than cute.
I was out of the picture and then I was
caught.
I feel closer to the people who are
watching.
Your father is cool.
Thank you.
But you treat your father badly.
You report this to your father.
Your father supports you.
That's good.
When did you go to that shrine?
I also go to the Kanagawa shrine.
Did you go to the Shichigo shrine there?
I also go to the Shichigo shrine.
You went there 65 years ago.
That's not true.
You two are good staff.
You have more staff than you two.
I'm sure.
I'm grateful to the staff.
I'm grateful to my brother.
We?
Then you will have more staff.
Will it be 35?
That's not true.
Do you have something?
I have a postcard.
Did you write it?
I will receive it.
Inoue will thank his brother.
He will finish the campaign.
You are the same as before.
You are dirty while eating.
This is finally completed.
This is the one-man heaven 33-person
thank you version.
Sorry for not coming back home yet
How does it feel to be the first one who
sees this scene
Even I haven't been care about him,
today
I took a shower, but no chance to see
him
Excuse.
Well
This is the most important part, right?
This is it, right?
Yes, that's right.
The bathroom.
Oh, that's right.
I don't think I've seen it.
I'm Nagi.
I'm Shizuka.
Nagi has his own hometown, and he's
loved by many people.
That's why he's such a wonderful person
now.
I think so.
But I think there are people who support
each other.
He's a great singer.
I used to be a model.
Really?
I was a crybaby.
I enjoyed it.
So when you decided to go for the 4th
song, you didn't even think about
lowering the key?
I didn't even think about lowering it.
But you got the key in the actual
performance.
I was the most excited.
But you were a bit more competitive.
Maybe.
But when I saw you singing on stage, I
thought you had the courage and the will
to do it.
Thank you.
I'll definitely do it. I'll be the first
one to go and give it to Nagi.
Are you embarrassed to be seen by your
current friends?
I'm so embarrassed.
Sing for the sake of the cruel angel.
I don't want to.
Inoue is very aggressive to Kaoru.
Because he's doing something great.
Are you doing great lately?
I'm not doing great lately.
But you don't have any friends like
that.
You should value the relationship
between siblings.
I should be careful about important
things at work.
I'm not going to leave Nagi at home.
I'm a little bit of a parent, but I
think I've discovered something new.
I'm glad.
It's amazing to know the roots until you
get in.
I like Nagi more.
I see.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for your comments.
I can't see your face.
I can't hear your message.
Next time, I'll write a big letter.
All right.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ume, how was it?
It was great.
I think personality is something that
can be developed by people who have been
involved in it.
Not only Nagi, but everyone, including
your family and loved ones, is taking
care of you.
So I'm very happy.
Ume's position is getting worse.
She's taking care of her precious
daughter.
That's the president's opinion.
She's the president of NOMIZAKA.
I think I have to take good care of her.
I want to raise everyone.
I'm glad you said that.
I want you to be a child.
I feel like I'm leaving you.
People here tend to want to see me as an
adult.
I want to be a child.
You're like a parent raising a child.
Ume is a mother here.
I'm a child, so I want to be a child.
You are a mother.
I want to be a child of this program.
I see.
I want to spill juice while sleeping.
I'll put something that looks like it's
going to spill next to you.
We're starting. Please welcome Banana
Man, the host of Nogizaka Koujitsu.
Ready, set...
I don't know.
It's still vague.
Himura-san, please tell us what we're
doing today.
Shittaka Grand Prix!
This time, the theme is a group of
members who love a certain topic.
But, there are members who don't know
the topic at all.
While answering the questions of the
members, they will pass the stage.
The Shittaka members will receive a
reward, a sweet.
Himura-san, this time...
I don't know.
So, Himura-san, if you win, you will
receive a reward.
I will get a fruit?
Not a fruit, but a sweet.
A sweet?
I did it!
But, if you don't know the topic at all,
you won't know the reason.
So, one hour before the recording, you
can study.
You can search on the Internet.
So, you can get some information.
I see.
The first topic is Totoro next to you.
Is there Totoro among these members?
Then, the members.
Yes.
Kubo.
I don't want to see.
Seimiya.
Kuromi.
Kuromi?
No, no, I don't want to see Kuromi.
You don't want to see Kuromi?
Matsuo.
I don't want to see Matsuo.
Only one member among these four has
never seen Totoro.
Will Kawasaki be able to see Totoro
through three questions?
Do you like Totoro?
We like him!
Everyone seems to be lying.
If you like him, you can talk about him
here.
The three of us will be very excited.
Has Totoro appeared on the show?
No way!
Who did you do it to?
Kawasaki, please look at the questions.
First question.
Please express your favorite scene with
a line.
I'm studying.
Let's start the discussion.
There are many.
It's hard to choose the best one.
It's okay.
My favorite scene is...
Come out, black-haired man.
If you don't come out, I'll pinch your
eyeballs.
That's fun.
Do you like that?
It's very impressive.
What's next?
I have one, too.
I like the atmosphere of standing.
That scene.
Totoro gets an umbrella from a cat bus.
I like that scene where Mei-chan lends
an umbrella.
Is there no line?
Have you ever seen it?
Totoro has a good point that is not a
line.
I was going to say that.
I like Kanta.
You didn't say it at first.
I joined in.
Kanta is a good actor.
I like Kanta.
I don't like Kanta's lines, but I like
his...
Hmm.
I like that.
I like the awkwardness of Kanta's lines.
I like the part where his mouth is like
a giblet.
I like his mouth.
I like Mei-chan's father's flower shop.
I like that.
I often imitate it.
How much did you get?
What's the second question?
What's your favorite pose?
I have to watch this.
It's a good pose.
Have you decided?
I have decided.
I like the first move.
You are like a veteran detective and a
newbie detective.
The first move is important.
Watch the first move.
It's important.
3, 2, 1.
What's that?
It's a cat bus.
It's a bus for Satsuki and Mei.
Is it a corn?
Yes, it is.
I see.
What about you, Semiya?
I like black.
Like a microphone.
Like a click.
Yes, like a click.
You don't have it when you go to a
store.
That's right.
What about you, Kuromi?
An umbrella.
I see.
I have another one.
I like it.
You have another one?
Can I?
Go ahead.
I like Totoro's sleeping scene.
I see.
What about you, Ayumu?
I like Totoro's hand that clings to
Totoro.
At night.
Yes.
That's good.
Are you okay?
Are you getting numb?
Yes.
Really?
I'm getting numb.
I am.
Who is the one who is getting numb?
The last question is...
Tell us the behind-the-scenes story of
this work.
This is a tough one.
Can I?
Go ahead, Kuromi.
Satsuki is very well-behaved.
She was supposed to be in the 4th grade,
but she was too well-behaved, so she was
in the 6th grade.
I see.
It's a secret story.
I don't think so.
There is no secret story.
Wait a minute.
If Kuromi doesn't tell us, she will be
popular.
I have a story.
My family has a dog named Bito.
Bito?
It was a dog that was easy to get along
with.
Is it a secret story?
It's not a secret story.
It's a secret story.
You like Kanta, don't you?
I like Mi-chan.
Mi-chan?
I like Mi-chan when I come to pick up
Satsuki-chan.
Is that a secret story?
It's a secret story.
I heard that I like Totoro.
When I was a member, Mae Tamura told me
that I looked like Rei-chan and Mei-
chan.
I was happy to hear that.
I'm not happy.
If you are one of the three, you are
lucky.
Did she see through the three questions?
What is the prediction of KAWASAKI?
It's KUBO.
KUBO seems to be able to hide his lies.
He also does radio.
I think he is good at talking.
He is planning to make this project
happen.
He is here with the staff's feelings.
Let's ask him.
It's KURO-MI.
why?
He only talks about the umbrella scene.
He only talked about KURO-MI.
I think he is a network person.
I think he said the information he
gathered in an hour.
Who has never seen Totoro?
Please raise your hands.
It's Kuromi!
Himawari-san is correct!
I love Totoro!
You like him too, right?
I watched Totoro every day when I was
little.
I only watched Totoro.
I went abroad when I was little.
I got a doll and I imitated the scene
with my sister.
Kuromi, you've never seen it?
I've never seen it.
So you've been talking on the internet
for an hour?
I'm on Wikipedia.
Hello, I'm Mayu Tamura.
I'm Renko Yamamoto.
I think the anime was really
interesting.
We are Buddy Daddies.
I thought you would say that.
I'm...
Hell Raku.
Please subscribe to our channel.